time 0ms: Simulator started for FCFS [Q: empty]
time 5ms: Process H arrived; added to ready queue [Q: H]
time 22ms: Process D arrived; added to ready queue [Q: H D]
time 33ms: Process A arrived; added to ready queue [Q: H D A]
time 44ms: Process F arrived; added to ready queue [Q: H D A F]
time 91ms: Process B arrived; added to ready queue [Q: H D A F B]
time 102ms: Process C arrived; added to ready queue [Q: H D A F B C]
time 108ms: Process G arrived; added to ready queue [Q: H D A F B C G]
time 242ms: Process E arrived; added to ready queue [Q: H D A F B C G E]
